Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- The Imposter, 1961; ref126; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - The Imposter, 1961; ref126_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 19, Folder 60)
- The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127; Salem, Atef; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 115 cm (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 115 cm (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 115 cm (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 120 cm (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 120 cm (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000030; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000031; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000032; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000033; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000034; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000035; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000036; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000037; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000038; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - The Seven Girls, 1961; ref127_000039; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 39)
- The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 75 x 100 cm (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 80 x 110 cm (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 75 x 100 cm (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 75 x 100 cm (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 75 x 100 cm (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 75 x 100 cm (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - The Sun Will Never Set, 1961; ref128_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 75 x 100 cm (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Without Tears, 1961; ref129; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Without Tears, 1961; ref129_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Zizette, 1961; ref130; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Zizette, 1961; ref130_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 20, Folder 84)
- Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131; 3464; Barakat, Henry
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000001; 4669; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000002; 4670; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000003; 4672; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000004; 4673; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000005; 4674; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000006; 4675; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000007; 4676; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000008; 4677; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000009; 4678; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000010; 4679; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000011; 4680; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000012; 4681; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000013; 4682; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000014; 4683; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Chains of Silk, 1962; ref131_000015; 4684; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
- Days Without Love, 1962; ref132; Mustafa, Hossam Dine; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Days Without Love, 1962; ref132_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 21, Folder 35)
- I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 85 x 130 cm (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 57 x 57 cm (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 57 x 57 cm (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - I am a Fugitive, 1962; ref133_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 60 x 90 cm (Box 21, Folder 55)
- Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Loyalty to Father, 1962; ref134_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135; Bedeer, Sayed; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Salwa in the Storm, 1962; ref135_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136; Tewfiq Saleh; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Struggle of Heroes, 1962; ref136_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 47)
- The Black Candles, 1962; ref137; Zulfiquar, Ezzeddine; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Black Candles, 1962; ref137_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - The Black Candles, 1962; ref137_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - The Black Candles, 1962; ref137_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - The Black Candles, 1962; ref137_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - The Black Candles, 1962; ref137_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 52)
- The Last Chance, 1962; ref138; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - The Last Chance, 1962; ref138_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 22, Folder 67)
- The Miracle, 1962; ref139; Al Imam, Hassan; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Miracle, 1962; ref139_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 12)
- The Olive Branch, 1962; ref140; Bedeer, Sayed; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Olive Branch, 1962; ref140_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - The Olive Branch, 1962; ref140_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 23, Folder 14)